Hi everyone
I'm gonna travel to 12 cities in the US, Canada and the UK in the next few months
To speak about my book, '12 Rules for Life' and other related issues
First I'll be in New York at the Beacon Theater at the end of March.
I'll announce the precise date in the next few days
I'll be going to the other 11 cities in May
I'll announce those dates very soon too.
Those cities include, Toronto
Washington, Chicago, Detroit
Denver
San Francisco, Seattle
London
Austin, Dallas and Phoenix
Tickets will be available for presale
February 21st if you go to my website JordanBPeterson.com and
Subscribe to the mailing list at the bottom of the page
You can register for presale notification. There's also an events page at JordanBPeterson.com
Tickets will go on sale for everyone on February 23rd.
Hope to see you at one of those venues
Thanks very much for the continued support and interest
bye-bye